Guide to the Pittsburgh Playhouse School of the Theater Records, 1934-1994 CTC.1981.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs and Negatives, 1935-1993; III.
  - Production Photographs, 1935-1993; 2.
    - See How They Run, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - See My Lawyer, 1940 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Send Me No Flowers, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Separate Tables, 1958 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - The Serpent, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Servant of Two Masters, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Seven Year Itch, 1958 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - She Loves Me, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - She Loves Me Not, 1948-1949 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - The Shadow Box, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Shoemaker and the Elves, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Shorty, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Side by Side by Sondheim, 1980-1981 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Silent Night Lonely Night, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1944 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Skylark, 1944 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Sleeping Beauty, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - The Sleeping Beauty, 1965-1966 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Small Miracle, 1945 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Smilin' Through, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Snow Queen and the Goblin, 1963-1964 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Snow White and Rose Red, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Soldier's Wife, 1946 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Solid Gold Cadillac, 1956 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - A Something Afoot, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - A Sound of Hunting, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - South Pacific, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - Spider, 1937-1938 (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - Speaking of Murder, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - Spread Eagle, 1935 (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - Springtime for Henry, 1936 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Strange Bedfellows, 1949-1950 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Streetcar Named Desire - Pictures of the car, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Streetcar Named Desire, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Streets of New York, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Subject Was Roses - Plus two negatives of stage shot, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Summer and Smoke, 1958 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Sunday in New York, 1963-1964 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Sun Up, 1943 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Suspect, 1942 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Take a Giant Step, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Take Her She's Mine, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Tartuffe, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Tartuffe, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - The Tavern, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Teahouse of the August Moon, 1957 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Teach Me How to Cry, 1957 (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Ten Minute Alibi, 1942 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - The Tenth Man, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - Tevya and His Daughters, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - Thank Your Stars, 1940 (Box 98, Folder 21)
    - They Walk Alone, 1945 (Box 98, Folder 22)
    - This Is My Valley, 1949 (Box 98, Folder 23)
    - Thousand Clowns, 1964 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Three Men on a Horse, 1952-1953 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Three Penny Opera, 1962 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Three Men on a Horse, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - The Time of the Cuckoo, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - The Time of Your Life, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Tiny Alice, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Titian, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - To the Point, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Tom Sawyer's Treasure Hunt, 1951 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Tonight at 8:30, 1939 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Tongue in Cheek, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Torchbearer, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - The Traitor, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Tree Grows in Brooklyn, 1958-1959 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Twelfth Night, 1980-1981 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Twelfth Night, 1964 (Box 99, Folder 16A)
    - Twentieth Century, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Two Gentlemen of Verona, 1985-1986 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Two on an Island, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Tunnel of Love, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - Two Blind Mice, 1950 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Two for the Seesaw, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - The Typist and the Tiger, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Under the Yum-Yum Tree, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Vanities, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Velvet Glove, 1951 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - View From the Bridge, 1957 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Vinegar Tree, 1943 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Visit to a Small Planet, 1958-1959 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Voice of the Turtle, 1952 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Wait Until Dark, 1969 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Waiting for Godot, 1959-1960 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Waiting for Godot, 198? (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - The Wedding, 1951 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - West Side Story, 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - West Side Story, - Stage sets, 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - What's the Rush?, 1956 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Where's Charley?, 1959-1960 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - White Sheep of the Family, 1954-1955 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - The White Steed, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Who Was That Lady I Saw You With?, 1959 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Who'll Save the Ploughboy?, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, 1966-1967 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Whose Life Is It Anyway?, 198? (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Wish You Were Here, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Witness for the Prosecution, 1957 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - The Women, 1955 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Wonderful Good, 1952 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Working, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - World of Sholom Aeichan (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Write Me a Murder, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Years Ago, 1948 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Yes My Darling Daughter, 1943 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - You Can't Take It With You, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Your Own Thing, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous plays - Unidentified (Box 102A, Folder 1-4)
    - And Niobe Wept - Act 1 Scene 2, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 1)
    - Administration Office, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 2)
    - Doctor In Spite of Himself - Scene 1, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 3)
    - Doctor In Spite of Himself - Scene 2, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 4)
    - Ghost of Yankee Doodle, Act 1, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 5)
    - The Hypochondriac, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 6)
    - I Want a Policeman - Act 2 Scene 2, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 7)
    - I Want a Policeman - Act 2, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 8)
    - It Can't Happen Here - Act 2 Scene 1, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 9)
    - It Can't Happen Here - Act 2 Scene 3, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 10)
    - Meet My Sister - Prologue, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 11)
    - Meet My Sister - Act 1, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 12-13)
    - Night Must Fall - Act 1, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 14)
    - Personal Appearance - Act 3, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 15)
    - Scenery Workshop, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 16)
    - Skelton, Hal, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 17)
    - Ten Minute Alibi, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 18)
    - Tonight at 8:30 - Hands Across the Sea, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 19)
    - Tonight at 8:30 - Ways and Means, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 20)
    - Tonight at 8:30 - Fumed Oak, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 21)
    - Unidentified - Male 'Shriners' gawking reclined female, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 22)
    - Unidentified - Playhouse Jr. production, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 23)
    - Unidentified - Cast at table eating and chatting, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 24)
    - Unidentified - Worried man with two other cast members, Oversize (Box 102B, Folder 25)
  - Negatives, 3.
    Arranged alphabetically by production title unless otherwise specified. At the end of the subseries, there is a small amount of Playhouse Jr. and miscellaneous negatives.
    - Accounting for Love (Box 103, Negatives 1-20)
    - Affairs of State (Box 103, Negatives 21-39)
    - After Hours (Box 103, Negatives 40-67)
    - Ah Wilderness! (Box 103, Negatives 68-93)
    - All My Sons (Box 103, Negatives 94-105)
    - Among Ourselves (Box 103, Negatives 106-119)
    - Anniversary Waltz (Box 103, Negatives 120-135)
    - Another Part of the Forest (Box 103, Negatives 136-152)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace (Box 103, Negatives 153-172)
    - At War with the Army (Box 103, Negatives 173-190)
    - Best Foot Forward (Box 103, Negatives 191-221)
    - Between Friends (Box 103, Negatives 222-272)
    - Born Yesterday (Box 104, Negatives 1)
    - Both Your Houses (Box 104, Negatives 2-17)
    - Boy Meets Girl (Box 104, Negatives 18-41)
    - Bus Stop (Box 104, Negatives 42-62)
    - Caine Mutiny Court Martial (Box 104, Negatives 63-97)
    - Capt. Brassfound's Conversion (Box 104, Negatives 98-120)
    - Champagne Complex (Box 104, Negatives 121-138)
    - Charm Kid (Box 104, Negatives 139-154)
    - Command Decision (Box 104, Negatives 155-172)
    - Crucible (Box 104, Negatives 173-194)
    - Curious Savage (Box 104, Negatives 195-212)
    - Dance for Joy (Box 104, Negatives 213-252)
    - Desperate Hours (Box 105, Negatives 1-23)
    - Detective Story (Box 105, Negatives 24-40)
    - Dial M for Murder (Box 105, Negatives 41-56)
    - Dream Girl (Box 105, Negatives 57-78)
    - Fifty Grand (Box 105, Negatives 79-105)
    - Girl from Wyoming (Box 105, Negatives 106-118)
    - Girl of the Via Flaminia (Box 105, Negatives 119-138)
    - Goodbye My Fancy (Box 105, Negatives 139-156)
    - Grand Guignol (Box 105, Negatives 157-180)
    - Happy Birthday (Box 105, Negatives 181-204)
    - Happy Time (Box 105, Negatives 205-223)
    - Hasty Heart (Box 105, Negatives 224-238)
    - Holly and the Ivy (Box 105, Negatives 259-259)
    - Home of the Brave (Box 106, Negatives 1-27)
    - Importance of Being Earnest (Box 106, Negatives 28-45)
    - Jenny Kissed Me (Box 106, Negatives 46-61)
    - Jest (Box 106, Negatives 62-83)
    - Joan of Lorraine (Box 106, Negatives 84-101)
    - John Loves Mary (Box 106, Negatives 102-122)
    - June Moon (Box 106, Negatives 123-142)
    - Juno and the Paycock (Box 106, Negatives 143-167)
    - King of Hearts (Box 106, Negatives 168-192)
    - Kiss for Cinderella (Box 106, Negatives 193-235)
    - Lady of Lely Square (Box 107, Negatives 1-22)
    - Late Christopher Bean (Box 107, Negatives 23-41)
    - Late George Apley (Box 107, Negatives 42-62)
    - Life with Mother (Box 107, Negatives 63-78)
    - Little Hut (Box 107, Negatives 79-97)
    - Little Wife (Box 107, Negatives 98-117)
    - Loud Red Patrick (Box 107, Negatives 118-130)
    - Love from Judy (Box 107, Negatives 131-158)
    - Man from Home (Box 107, Negatives 159-175)
    - Macbeth (Box 107, Negatives 176-190)
    - Mister Roberts (Box 107, Negatives 191-243)
    - Morning's at Seven (Box 107, Negatives 244-260)
    - Mousetrap (Box 108, Negatives 1-20)
    - My Three Angels (Box 108, Negatives 21-57)
    - Of All Things (Box 108, Negatives 58-79)
    - Of Mice and Men (Box 108, Negatives 80-106)
    - Off the Top (Box 108, Negatives 107-130)
    - Oh Men! Oh Women! (Box 108, Negatives 131-151)
    - On the Lighter Side (Box 108, Negatives 152-185)
    - Lighter Side (Box 108, Negatives 186-198)
    - On Your Mark (Box 108, Negatives 199-228)
    - Once Upon a Mattress (Box 108, Negatives 229-230)
    - Our Town (Box 108, Negatives 231-246)
    - Payment Deferred (Box 109, Negatives 1-19)
    - Peg O' My Heart (Box 109, Negatives 20-49)
    - Present Laughter (Box 109, Negatives 50-68)
    - Poor Nut (Box 109, Negatives 69-87)
    - Pygmalion (Box 109, Negatives 88-109)
    - Queen's Husband (Box 109, Negatives 110-130)
    - Reclining Figure (Box 109, Negatives 131-155)
    - Remains To Be Seen (Box 109, Negatives 156-177)
    - Remarkable Mr. Penny (Box 109, Negatives 178-198)
    - Remember Me (Box 109, Negatives 199-211)
    - Roomful of Roses (Box 109, Negatives 212-234)
    - Royal Family (Box 109, Negatives 235-258)
    - Sabrina Fair (Box 110, Negatives 1-25)
    - See How They Run (Box 110, Negatives 26-46)
    - She Loves Me Not (Box 110, Negatives 47-61)
    - Shorty (Box 110, Negatives 62-81)
    - Solid Gold Cadillac (Box 110, Negatives 82-103)
    - Sound of Hunting (Box 110, Negatives 104-124)
    - Strange Bedfellows (Box 110, Negatives 125-144)
    - Take a Giant Step (Box 110, Negatives 145-180)
    - Teach Me To Cry (Box 110, Negatives 181-191)
    - Teahouse of the August Moon (Box 110, Negatives 192-212)
    - Three To One (Box 111, Negatives 1-42)
    - Three Men On a Horse (Box 111, Negatives 43-64)
    - Time of the Cuckoo (Box 111, Negatives 65-86)
    - Torchbearers (Box 111, Negatives 87-109)
    - Traitor (Box 111, Negatives 110-127)
    - Twentieth Century (Box 111, Negatives 128-133)
    - Two Blind Mice (Box 111, Negatives 134-152)
    - Two on an Island (Box 111, Negatives 153-187)
    - Velvet Glove (Box 111, Negatives 188-204)
    - View from the Bridge (Box 111, Negatives 205-231)
    - Voice of the Turtle (Box 111, Negatives 232-249)
    - Water Witch (Box 112, Negatives 1-19)
    - The Wedding (Box 112, Negatives 20-22)
    - What's the Rush (Box 112, Negatives 23-82)
    - White Sheep of the Family (Box 112, Negatives 83-101)
    - White Steed (Box 112, Negatives 102-118)
    - Witness for the Prosecution (Box 112, Negatives 119-151)
    - Women (Box 112, Negatives 152-179)
    - Wonderful Good (Box 112, Negatives 180-220)
    - Years Ago (Box 112, Negatives 221-238)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Aladdin (Box 113, Negatives 1-11)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Ali Baba (Box 113, Negatives 12-19)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Arthur and the Sword (Box 113, Negatives 20-27)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Cinderella (Box 113, Negatives 28-35)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Circus Day (Box 113, Negatives 36-46)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Cricket Farm (Box 113, Negatives 47-52)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Flibberty Gibbet (Box 113, Negatives 53-59)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Forest Ring (Box 113, Negatives 60-71)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Greensleeves Magic (Box 113, Negatives 72-80)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Hurricane Island (Box 113, Negatives 81-89)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - King of the Golden River (Box 113, Negatives 90-97)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - King Midas (Box 113, Negatives 98-105)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Land of the Dragon (Box 113, Negatives 106-113)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Little Red Riding Hood (Box 113, Negatives 114-124)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Mystery at Old Fort (Box 113, Negatives 125-128)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Mysterious Sandalwood Box (Box 113, Negatives 129-141)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Panda and Spy (Box 113, Negatives 142-152)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Papa Popino (Box 113, Negatives 153-158)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Pied Piper (Box 113, Negatives 159-161)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Puss in Boots (Box 113, Negatives 162-173)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Rumpelstiltskin (Box 113, Negatives 174-184)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Robin Hood (Box 113, Negatives 185-191)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Shoemaker and the Elves (Box 113, Negatives 192-199)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Snow Queen (Box 113, Negatives 200-209)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Titian (Box 113, Negatives 210-213)
    - Playhouse Jr. Productions - Tom Sawyer (Box 113, Negatives 214-218)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Art show (Photos of unidentified exhibited paintings) (Box 113, Negatives 219-233)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Burleigh Night (Box 113, Negatives 234-241)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Civic Night (Box 114, Negatives 1-13)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Children's Theater (Box 114, Negatives 14-26)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Jones, Shirley (Box 114, Negatives 27-32)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Murals (Box 114, Negatives 33-39)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - New Theater (Box 114, Negatives 40-58)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Norris, Janice (Box 114, Negatives 58-78)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - On Tour (Box 114, Negatives 79-107)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Oklahoma! - Opening Night (Box 114, Negatives 108-135)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Playhouse Expansion (Box 114, Negatives 136-157)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Promotion (Box 114, Negatives 158-170)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Rauh, Helen W. (Box 114, Negatives 174-190)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Restaurant (Box 114, Negatives 191-217)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Scholarship, Mercy Hospital (Box 114, Negatives 218-220)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - School (Box 114, Negatives 221-232)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - School Productions (Box 114, Negatives 233-249)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Social Events (Box 115, Negatives 1-29)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Staff (Box 115, Negatives 30-47)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - G. Wood/K. Welch (Box 115, Negatives 48-52)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - After Hours (Box 115, Negatives 53-72)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Unidentified stage sets (Box 115, Negatives 73-145)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Unidentified people (Box 115, Negatives 146-225)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Interior Shots (Box 115, Negatives 226-267)
  - Photo Albums, 1946-1964; 4.
    These five photo albums contain photographs of nearly every Pittsburgh Playhouse production between the years 1946-1964. The items listed within each album are the productions that are represented in that particular album. The photographs are usually 4 by 5 inches and there can sometimes be 10 or more for each production.
    - Album 1, 1946-1951 (Box 115, Portfolio 1)
      - Both Your Houses, 1946; 1.
      - Boys Meets Girl, 1946; 2.
      - Juno and the Paycock, 3.
      - Lady of Lely Square, 1947; 4.
      - After Hours, 1947; 5.
      - Late George Apley, 1947; 5.
      - June Moon, 1948; 6.
      - Another Part of the Forest, 1948; 7.
      - A Sound of Hunting, 1948; 8.
      - All My Sons, 1948; 9.
      - Years Ago, 1948; 10.
      - The Girl from Wyoming, 1948; 11.
      - Joan of Lorraine, 1948; 12.
      - Shorty, 1948; 13.
      - She Loves Me Not, 1949; 14.
      - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1949; 15.
      - Command Decision, 1949; 16.
      - Anna Christie, 1949; 17.
      - Of All Things, 1949; 18.
      - Remember Me, 1949; 19.
      - The Traitor, 1949; 20.
      - This is My Valley, 1949; 21.
      - Strange Bedfellows, 1950; 22.
      - Grand Guignol, 1950; 23.
      - Captain Brassbound's Conversion, 1950; 24.
      - Two Blind Mice, 1950; 25.
      - Fifty Grand, 1950; 26.
      - Jenny Kissed Me, 1950; 27.
      - Goodbye My Fancy, 28.
      - At War With the Army, 1950; 29.
      - The Charm Kid, 1951; 30.
      - Detective Story, 1951; 31.
      - The Wedding, 1951; 32.
      - The Velvet Glove, 1951; 33.
      - On Your Mark, 1951; 34.
      - Arsenic and Old Lace, 1951; 35.
      - The Curious Savage, 1951; 36.
      - Water Witch, 1951; 37.
    - Album 2, 1952-1954 (Box 115, Portfolio 2)
      - Voice of the Turtle, 1952; 1.
      - Wonderful Good, 1952; 2.
      - Three Men on a Horse, 1952-1953; 3.
      - The White Steed, 1953; 4.
      - Best Foot Forward, 1953; 5.
      - The Holly and the Ivy, 1952-1953; 6.
      - Remains To Be Seen, 1952; 7.
      - Dance for Joy, 8.
      - Ah Wilderness!, 1952; 9.
      - The Happy Time, 1952; 10.
      - Present Laughter, 1952; 11.
      - Twentieth Century, 1952; 12.
      - Peg O'My Heart, 1952; 13.
      - The Royal Family, 1953; 14.
      - Life with Mother, 1953; 15.
      - Payment Deferred, 1953; 16.
      - Three to One, 1953; 17.
      - The Little Wife, 1953; 18.
      - Mister Roberts, 1953; 19.
      - John Loves Mary, 1953; 20.
      - Two on an Island, 1953; 21.
      - Affairs of State, 1953-1954; 22.
      - A Kiss for Cinderella, 1954; 23.
      - Time of the Cuckoo, 1954; 24.
      - Take a Giant Step, 1954; 25.
      - The Queen's Husband, 1954; 26.
      - Happy Birthday, 1954; 27.
      - Home of the Brave, 1954; 28.
      - Between Friends, 1954; 29.
    - Album 3, 1954-1956 (Box 115, Portfolio 3)
      - Pygmalion, 1954; 1.
      - Of Mice and Men, 1954; 2.
      - White Sheep of the Family, 1955; 3.
      - Sabrina Fair, 1955; 4.
      - Girl on the Via Flaminia, 1955; 5.
      - The Women, 1955; 6.
      - Late Christopher Bean, 1955; 7.
      - The Crucible, 1955; 8.
      - The Little Hut, 1955; 9.
      - The Lighter Side, 1955; 10.
      - Caine Mutiny Court Martial, 1955; 11.
      - King of Hearts, 1955; 12.
      - Reclining Figure, 1955; 13.
      - Remarkable Mr. Pennypacker, 1955; 14.
      - Dial M for Murder, 1955; 15.
      - Our Town, 1955; 16.
      - Accounting for Love, 1955; 17.
      - Oh Men! Oh Women!, 1956; 18.
      - Among Ourselves, 1956; 19.
      - The Jest, 1956; 20.
      - Morning's at Seven, 1956; 21.
      - The Torchbearers, 1956; 22.
      - Roomful of Roses, 1956; 23.
      - What's the Rush?, 1956; 24.
      - Champagne Complex, 1956; 25.
      - Solid Gold Cadillac, 1956; 26.
    - Album 4, 1956-1961 (Box 115, Portfolio 4)
      - Bus Stop, 1957; 1.
      - Anniversary Waltz, 1956; 2.
      - The Mouse Trap, 1956; 3.
      - The Man From Home, 1957; 4.
      - Teach Me How to Cry, 1957; 5.
      - Love From Judy, 1957; 6.
      - The Loud Red Patrick, 1957; 7.
      - View from the Bridge, 1957; 8.
      - Teahouse of the August Moon, 1957; 9.
      - Witness for the Prosecution, 1957; 10.
      - Off the Top, 1957; 11.
      - Epitaph for George Dillon, 1959; 12.
      - Make a Million, 1959; 13.
      - Waiting for Godot, 1959-1960; 14.
      - The Gazebo, 1960; 15.
      - Tevya and His Daughter, 1960; 16.
      - Midsummer Night's Dream, 1960; 17.
      - Sailor Beware, 1960; 18.
      - Open Season, 1960; 19.
      - Mighty Mikko and the Fox, 1959; 20.
      - Jack and the Bean Stalk, 1960; 21.
      - The Dark at the Top of the Stairs, 1960; 22.
      - Golden Fleecing, 1960; 23.
      - Silent Night Lonely Night, 1960; 24.
      - Cheating at Love, 1960; 25.
      - Leave It to Jane, 1960-1961; 26.
      - Pictures in the Hallway, 1961; 27.
      - Marriage-Go-Round, 1961; 28.
      - Hamlet, 1961; 29.
      - Between Two Thieves, 1961; 30.
      - Two for the Seesaw, 1961; 31.
      - Babes in Arms, 1961; 32.
      - Tartuffe, 1961; 33.
      - Roar Like a Dove, 1961; 34.
      - Mysterious Arabian Night, 1960; 35.
      - The Legend of the Harlequin, 1961; 36.
      - Adventures of the Puppet Prince, 1961; 37.
      - Big Fish, Little Fish, 1961; 38.
      - The Deadly Game, 1961; 39.
      - The Period of Adjustment, 1961; 40.
      - Nude With Violin, 1961; 41.
      - Monique, 1961; 42.
      - The Prisoner, 1961; 43.
      - Little Mary Sunshine, 1961; 44.
    - Album 5, 1961-1964 (Box 115, Portfolio 5)
      - The Desk Set, 1961; 1.
      - Under the Yum Yum Tree, 1961; 2.
      - Playboy of the Western World, 1962; 3.
      - Andersonville Trial, 1962; 4.
      - The World of Shalom Aleichen, 1962; 5.
      - The Pair of Spectacles, 1962; 6.
      - Macbeth, 1962; 7.
      - Three Penny Opera, 1962; 8.
      - The American Dream and The Zoo Story, 1962; 9.
      - South Pacific, 1962; 10.
      - The Pleasure of His Company, 1962; 11.
      - The Emperor's New Clothes, 1961; 12.
      - Cinderella, 1962; 13.
      - Beauty and the Beast, 1962; 14.
      - The Pied Piper of Hamlin, 1962; 15.
      - Oh Kay!, 1962; 16.
      - Critic's Choice, 1962; 17.
      - Who'll Save the Ploughboy?, 1962; 18.
      - Write Me a Murder, 1962; 19.
      - Bye Bye Birdie, 1963; 20.
      - First Night, 1963; 21.
      - The Fantasticks, 1963; 22.
      - Fifth Season, 1963; 23.
      - Anna Kleiber, 1963; 24.
      - Taming of the Shrew, 1963; 25.
      - Come Blow Your Horn, 1963; 26.
      - The Caretaker, 1963; 27.
      - Make a Note of It, 1963; 28.
      - Pinocchio, 1962; 29.
      - My Friend and the Fox, 1963; 30.
      - The Elves and the Shoemaker, 1963; 31.